wpadvancedads.com 2018-11-20

# Privacy Policy - Advanced Ads

This policy helps you to understand how we collect, share and use information about you. It applies to this website as well as to services and products connected with it (e.g., our _Advanced Ads_ plugins).

If you do not agree with this policy, do not access or use our services or interact with any other aspect of our business.

Our aim is to offer this information as complete and helpful as possible, so please [reach out](https://wpadvancedads.com/support/) in case something is missing or incomprehensible.

When we use “Advanced Ads”, “we” or “us” in this policy we refer to webgilde GmbH, the company behind and services offered by it.

## How and where we handle your information

We have access to information about you when you give it to us, use our services and products, and when other services provide it to us.

### Account and purchase information

For each purchase on wpadvancedads.com, an account is created automatically. It contains the information you gave us during the checkout and combines a history of your purchase and license activity (e.g., when you enable a license for one of our product). We are legally bound to store this information for 10 years. You can request the removal of your account information after 10 years of complete inactivity.

By purchasing you agree that we

  * Send you important account, order, service information, but not impersonal newsletters.
  * Respond to your queries, refund requests, or complaints.
  * Process payments to prevent fraudulent transactions and log downloads and license checks. We do this on the basis of our legitimate business interests.
  * Set up and administer your account, provide technical and/or customer support, and to verify your identity.

Additionally, we may also collect location and traffic data (including IP address) because we are legally obliged to charge you taxes based on this information and keep a record of it,

You can update your account information [here](https://wpadvancedads.com/account/edit-profile/).

We are using external services to process your payment. These services store the information you give them either on their sites or during the checkout. If you don‘t accept these services then please reach out to use and ask for wire transfer details.

We neither store nor have access to your credit card number.

We only give access to your account information to those members of our team who need it to support you, need access to payment information for accounting or maintain appropriate features on our website.

### User activity (e.g., Comments)

Please be aware that interaction with our websites, e.g., commenting or using forms, most likely leaves data and personal information. We store this information on our own server (comments) or using third party services (forms, help desks).

When you leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also your IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available [here](https://automattic.com/privacy/). After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

You can request this data or its removal. The latter can be limited by legal obligation and depends on the nature of the appropriate data.

### Passive user activity, website tracking, and cookies

By using our websites, you might also leave information.

Our website uses cookies to show different information to different users (e.g., based on their browser size, number of page impressions) for a better user experience. These cookies can last up to ten years.

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

By visiting this website you agree to accept cookies.

Our websites are using  **Google Analytics** , a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses “cookies”, which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States.

Google will use this information on behalf of the operator of this website for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing them other services relating to website activity and internet usage.

IP-anonymisation is activated. We also made use of the feature that automatically removes personalized information after 50 months.

You can also opt-out from being tracked by Google Analytics with effect for the future by downloading and installing Google Analytics Opt-out browser addon for your current web browser: <http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en>.

We are using a service called **Hotjar** to analyze the performance and conversion on this site.

You can learn more about Hotjar and the data it stores in their [privacy policy](https://www.hotjar.com/privacy).

You can learn more about the cookies Hotjar stores from their [cookie information](https://www.hotjar.com/cookies) or opt out of the Hotjar cookies [on this page](https://www.hotjar.com/opt-out).

We may enable **server logs** if needed (e.g., to prevent or avert an attack on our server). Server logs contain the time, IP address, user agent, and page visited. We are keeping them only as long as needed. We are not cross-referencing them with other information.

Our products may contain attributes links to our website (e.g., manual) which we use to determine a) which features we should improve so that users need less documentation and b) which pages on our site are worth keeping updated and c) which pages we can remove, because they are no longer used.

We are using a firewall from **Sucuri** to secure and prevent our websites from attacks and hacks. We do this to protect the availability of our service and user data. They use the visitor’s IP address in encrypted form.

We use **Stripe** for payment, analytics, and other business services. Stripe collects identifying information about the devices that connect to its services. Stripe uses this information to operate and improve the services it provides to us, including for fraud detection. You can learn more about Stripe and read its privacy policy at <https://stripe.com/privacy>.

### Support Channels

We are using **Help Scout** to manage user communication (except our newsletter) and support. The advantage of mentioned service is to have all our conversations at one place, which allows us to look into similar and previous conversations to help you.

The [support forum for Advanced Ads on wordpress.org](https://wordpress.org/support/plugin/advanced-ads) is not in our sphere of influence. If you don’t agree with their terms and [privacy policy](https://wordpress.org/about/privacy/) you may use [our own support form](https://wpadvancedads.com/support/).

### Logins to your website

When helping you with our products or services we might request a login to your website. This is completely voluntary to you.

Please be aware that the login credentials might be saved in E-Mails, our help desk and possibly a project management tool and therefore are not 100% save.

We, therefore, recommend creating a new account for the purpose of our work with the necessary user rights only and disable it or change the password as soon as we finished the job.

### Newsletter

We maintain a newsletter with information about updates, asking for feedback or run promotions regarding Advanced Ads. By subscribing, you agree that we may process your information in accordance with these terms.

To prevent misuse, a double opt-in is required, which means that you will receive an email to confirm your subscription before we can send you anything else.

Once you are subscribed, you can change your mind at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link in the footer of any email you receive from us, or by [contacting us](https://wpadvancedads.com/support/).

We use MailChimp as our marketing automation platform. By subscribing, you acknowledge that the information you provide will be transferred to MailChimp for processing in accordance with their [Privacy Policy](https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/) and [Terms](https://mailchimp.com/legal/terms/).

### wordpress.org

Some of our plugins are hosted on wordpress.org. Before viewing, downloading and using these plugins you should be aware that their [privacy policy](https://wordpress.org/about/privacy/) applies.

You can get a copy of the Advanced Ads plugin hosted on wordpress.org directly from us. However, as with all other plugins, your hosted WordPress site will send data to wordpress.org regarding updates of the plugins.

### Other communication

We may use additional services like Twitter or Facebook. Their usage is not necessary to get in contact with us or to use our services and product. You are bound to the privacy policies of external services if you use them to get in contact with us.

### YouTube

We publish and include Videos from YouTube from Google LLC, 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA.  
Privacy Policy can be found on: <https://policies.google.com/privacy>

## How we store and secure information we collect

Please notice, that using the internet is not a 100 percent secure and neither we nor anyone else can guarantee that your data cannot be access by others. Being said, this doesn‘t mean that we don’t take any measures known to us to secure your information.

We limit storing information as much as possible, meaning that we only enable and use services and information as long as we have a legal obligation or vital or legitimate interest in them.

Among the steps we take to secure your data are:

  * using HTTPS on all of our websites
  * using either European service providers or those who fall under the Privacy Shield
  * limiting access to this data to only those team members and service providers who absolutely need them

## How to access and control your information

You have the right to request a copy of your information, object to our use of your information, request the deletion or restriction of your information, or to request your information in a structured, electronic format. The tools and processes of these requests might differ by their nature and only be possible through a third party.

Your request may be limited, for example, if it would reveal information about another party, or we are obligated to keep it by law or legitimate interests. If you have unresolved concerns, you may have the right to complain to a data protection authority.

## List of Sub-Processors

We are using a number of third-party tools and services to handle or store data. You may find them in the list below with links to further information.

Help Scout| [Privacy Policy](https://www.helpscout.net/company/legal/privacy/)  
---|---  
df.eu (Hosting)| [Privacy Policy (German)](https://www.df.eu/de/datenschutz/)  
Mailchimp| [Privacy Policy,](https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/) [Terms](https://mailchimp.com/legal/terms/).  
Google Analytics| [Privacy Information](https://policies.google.com/privacy)  
Hotjar| [Privacy Policy](https://www.hotjar.com/privacy)  
PayPal| [Privacy Policy](https://www.paypal.com/privacy)  
Stripe| [Privacy Policy](https://stripe.com/privacy)  
Sucuri| [Privacy Policy](https://sucuri.net/privacy)  
YouTube| [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy)  
  
## Changes to this Privacy Policy

We may change this privacy policy from time to time. If changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice on this website.

## Contact

Do you have questions regarding our privacy policy? Please reach out to the person in charge listed below via our [contact form](https://wpadvancedads.com/support/).

webgilde GmbH  
Thomas Maier  
Dorfstraße 18d  
17495 Züssow OT Ranzin, Germany
